https://www.gshgroup.com/privacy-policy/

View Our Services Connect with GSHDownload "5 Things You Need To Know When Considering A Facilities Management Provider" Home > Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy for GSH GroupThis Privacy Policy was last updated on 6/13/18.Our Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of our website, located at https://www.gshgroup.com/, and the information we provide you via the “Website” or the “Service”. Any terms not defined in our Privacy Policy, have the meaning as specified in our Terms of Use accessible at https://www.gshgroup.com/terms-of-use/.Your PrivacyOur Website follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.DefinitionsPersonal Data: Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).Usage Data: Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Website or Service or from the Website or Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.Data Controller: Data Controller means a natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.Data Processors (or Service Providers): Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.Data Subject: Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.User: The User is the individual using our Website or Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Website and our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Website or Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: Email address, Name, Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City, Cookies and Usage Data.We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.Usage DataWe may also collect information how the Website or Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Website or Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Website or Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Website and Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website or Service.Examples of Cookies we use: session cookies (we use these cookies to operate our Website Service) and preference cookies (we use these cookies to remember your preferences and various settings).Use of DataWe use the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain our Website or ServiceTo notify you about changes to our Website or ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Website or ServiceTo monitor the usage of our Website or ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTo provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such informationRetention of DataWe will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Website and Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.Transfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Disclosure Of DataBusiness Transaction. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.Disclosure for Law Enforcement. Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).Security Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), GSH Group’s legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.GSH Group may process your Personal Data because:We need to perform a contract with youYou have given us permission to do soThe processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rightsFor payment processing purposesTo comply with the lawYour Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. GSH Group aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at info@gshgroup.com.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of your Personal Data in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where GSH Group relied on your consent to process your personal information.Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).Information you provide us by registeringIn addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Website, to become a subscriber to the Website or Service such as requesting our newsletter or submitting an inquiry, you may need to create a personal profile. You may receive information by registering on the Website and entering your email address and other details. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Website and Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Website and Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Website or Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Links To Other SitesOur Website or Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Website or Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We may notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We may let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website or Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by using the contact information we provided on our Contact page.NEWS: GSH Group Awarded the Gold Award of Excellence in FM 2020 by the Global FM Trade OrganizationRead More About GSH ABOUT
GSH Services SERVICES
Contact Us CONTACT
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
